King, Edward Papers 5263
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edward King Papers
1885
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
King, Edward
5263
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Personal papers and minutes of the Central Labor Union of New York City and Vicinity.
5557189
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 08, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of Edward King's personal papers and minutes of the Central Labor Union of New York City and Vicinity.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
King, Edward, 1821-1885; AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council
5557189
- Biographical Notes and Photograph, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 Photograph
- Memorial Meeting 1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Program of the Memorial Meeting in Honor of Edward King, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By The Edward King Memorial Committee. January 28, 1923. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to Contributors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By The Edward King Memorial Committee. August 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Speech at the Memorial Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Gregory Weinstein. January 28, 1923. Item is in English.
- Correspondence 1889-1905, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Central Labor Union Constitution and By-Laws, 1888; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the Central Labor Union of New York and Vicinity, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Central Labor Union of New York and Vicinity. Item is in English.
- Central Labor Union Review 1888, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Central Labor Union Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Central Labor Union Minutes 1885, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Criticism of "Pantomime" Article 1870, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pantomime, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Joun Hood. Typescript of article. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Criticism of John Hood's Article "Pantomime", Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Edward King. Typescript of article. Item is in English.
- The Floral Teachings and Aspirations of Labor 1907, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Moral Teachings and Aspirations of Labor: Are They Compatible With the Teachings of the Church?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Edward King. Typescript of text incorporated into an article by James P. Archibald, printed in The Painter and Decorator, January, 1907. Item is in English.
- The Standard Series on Self-Culture, 1880; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: On Self-Culture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By John Stuart Blackie. The Standard Series no.11 (1880: Apr. 13). Item is in English.